圣诞到来了
Christmas time is here
幸福又愉快
Happiness and cheer
这是一年中
Fun for all
孩子们
That children call
最欢乐的时光
Their favorite time of year
雪花在空中飞舞
Snowflakes in the air
到处都充满了欢声笑语
Carols everywhere
旧时的节拍
Olden times
与古老的歌谣
And ancient rhymes
分享着爱与梦的旋律
Of love and dreams to share
雪橇铃声飘散在空中
Sleigh bells in the air
世间如此美好
Beauty everywhere
火炉边的圣诞时光
Yuletide by the fireside
满是欢乐的回忆
And joyful memories there
圣诞到来了
Christmas time is here
我们期待着它的到来
We'll be trouting near
哦 我们总是可以看到
Oh that we could always see
人们伴着这样的心情度过新的一年
Such spirit through the year
雪橇铃声飘散在空气中
Sleigh bells in the air
世间如此美好
Beauty everywhere
火炉边的圣诞时光
Yuletide by the fireside
满是欢乐的回忆
And joyful memories there
圣诞到来了
Christmas time is here
我们期待着它的到来
We'll be trouting near
哦 我们总是可以看到
Oh that we could always see
人们伴着这样的心情度过新的一年
Such spirit through the year
哦 我们总是可以看到
Oh that we could always see
人们伴着这样的心情度过新的一年
Such spirit through the year